jigidi.com 2019-04-25

# Privacy Policy

## Introduction

This Policy details our commitment to protect the privacy of individuals who visit Jigidi. 

Whether you are a user of Jigidi.com and or our Jigidi app, our Privacy Policy describes for you: 

  * The information we collect 
  * How that information may be used
  * With whom it may be shared
  * Our choices about such uses and disclosures

By using our website or app, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. We, therefore, encourage you to read it carefully when either using our website, app or transacting business with us. 

If you have any questions about our privacy practices, please refer to the end of this Privacy Policy for information on how to contact us. 

## What information do we collect?

We collect information about you in two ways: 

  * Data you provide to us when you use web forms on our site. Such as when you create a profile or ask for support.
  * Data gathered from the way you interact with our site.

### Data you provide to us

The types of personal information that we collect directly from you depend on how you interact with the site and may include: 

  * Account login credentials, such as username and password.
  * Your name, email, gender, and age (all of which are optional).
  * The images you upload and turn into jigsaw puzzles.
  * Comments and messages you write to us and other users of the site.

This information is only collected in order to provide the service the information is intended for. We do never share this information with anyone. 

### Data gathered from the way you interact with our site

Our service may automatically collect information about how you and your device interact with the site, including but not limited to: 

  * Approximately geographical location
  * Browser, version of the browser and operating system
  * Whether there is a flash player installed
  * Your computers IP address
  * Which pages you visit on Jigidi
  * How long you have been on Jigidi
  * How much time you spent on one page 
  * How long it has been since you last visited Jigidi
  * Which pages you arrived from when you came to Jigidi

Information collected on behavior is anonymous which means, we receive and analyze percentage figures. 

## What do we use your information for?

The information we collect from you may be used the following ways: 

  * To improve our site 
  * To personalize your experience 
  * To improve support 
  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature 
  * To display advertisements that may be personalized. 
  * To process transactions (your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased service requested). 

## How do we protect your information?

We take precautions to safeguard your personal information against loss, theft and misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction through the use of appropriate technical and organizational measures. 

When you purchase a service from us we use PayPal and all information disclosed during the transaction is handled by PayPal in accordance with their [Privacy Policy](https://www.paypal.com/us/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full). 

After a transaction is complete, only your full name and email are stored on our servers. 

## Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

Non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. 

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information, except for to trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you - so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. 

We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. 

## Do we use cookies?

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember specific information. 

We use both session and persistent cookies on the site, and we use different types of cookies to run the site: 

  * _Essential cookies._ Necessary for the operation of the site. We may use essential cookies to authenticate users, prevent fraudulent use, or offer site features. 
  * _Analytical cookies._ Allow us to recognize and count the number of visitors and see how visitors move around the site when using it. This helps us improve the way the site works. 
  * _Functionality cookies._ Used to recognize you when you return to the site. This enables us to personalize our content for you. 
  * _Targeting cookies._ Record your visit to the site, the pages you have visited, and the links you have followed. We will use this information to make the site and the more relevant to your interests. 

In addition to our cookies, we may also use various third-party cookies to report usage statistics of the site and refine marketing efforts. 

  * _Tracking cookies._ Follow on-site behavior and tie it to other metrics allowing a better understanding of usage habits. 
  * _Advertising cookies._ Google use cookies which enables them to serve personalized ads to you based on your interests. You may [opt out of Ads Personalization](https://www.google.com/ads/preferences/) and read more about [Google's advertising privacy policy](https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads). 

Personalized ads are disabled for users in the EEA (European Economic Area). 

## What are your choices regarding cookies

If you'd like to delete cookies or instruct your web browser to delete or refuse cookies, please visit the help pages of your web browser. 

Please note, however, that if you delete cookies or refuse to accept them, you might not be able to use some or all of the features we offer. You may not be able to log in, store your preferences, and some of our pages might not display properly. 

## Your Consent

You consent to our privacy policy by using our website. 

## Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page and update the Privacy Policy modification date below. 

This policy was last modified on 28. May 2018 

## How to contact us

If you have any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us
